Guide to the Papers of Richard Phillips Feynman, 1933-1988
Archives
- Group II
  - Section VII: Working Notes And Calculations
    - Calculations on QCD [?] 1982 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - "Closed Loop and Tree Diagrams" [pub. 1972] (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Chemistry (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Computers, miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Computers and QED ca 1984 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Computer Notebook and Other Material 1983-84 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Constructing a Triangle Using a Compass (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Cosmology and Stars ca 1968 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Coulomb Propagator (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Cylindrical Sedimentation (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - DEMON Computer Algorithm and other notes (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - DNA (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Defense, Nuclear War (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Density Matrices [?] (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Diagram Relationships (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Dirac Equation, Rotation of Matrix Elements (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - "Discussion After Schild's talk" 26 July 19[?] (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Dispersion (Box 65, Folder Folders 2-3)
    - Dissipative Linear Systems (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Eigenstates and Energies [?] (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Electron-Nucleon Interaction (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Experimental Data, Decay ca 1957-61 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Extreme Relativistic Electrodynamics (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Feynman Talk Graphs (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Feynman's "Miscellaneous" File (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Field Effects ca 1950 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Fluid Motion, Viscous (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Flux Lines 5/10/67 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Fourier Transform of υ(κ2) (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Future Computing Machines (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Gaussian Signals/Information Theory [?] (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Glacial Ice, Argon, Numbers (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Gravity (Box 66, Folder Folders 2-3)
    - Gravity in Astronomy and Lecture on Curved Space (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Gravity Notepad [?] (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Gravity Waves, Virtual Particles [?] various (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Gravitational Equations, Yang Mills (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Group Theory, Quantum Fundamentals (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Helium (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Helium 3 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Helium, Rotating (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - High energy E + M (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Integrating the Action Inside a Rectangle 3/4/82 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Integrals Notepad (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Ising Model (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Ithaca Meeting 8/71, Representations of The Lorentz Graph 3/73 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Kaon [κ] Decay (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Kinds of Systems ca 1980 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Lamb shift, notes (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Large Mass Interactions in QCD 5/22/79-77/7/79 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Lattices [?] (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Lorentz Group 1965 and undated (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Calculations (Box 68, Folder Folders 3-6)
    - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Notes ca 1979-84 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Notes
      - Helium, Superconductivity, etc. (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Mostly QED [?] (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Mostly Quantum Mechanics ca 1950s-1960s (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Notes from R.P.F's Desk (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Particles, QED I, various dates (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - Particles, QED II, various dates (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Plasma, Particles, Astrophysics ca 1970s (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Notes on Computers (folder 3) n.d.; (folder 4) ca 1984 (Box 70, Folder Folders 3-4)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, Quarks, QED, various (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Technical Notes (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Meson Scattering (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Mobility (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Muon (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - μ°⇒3π decay July 1966 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Negative Probabilities (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Negative Probabilities 18 Feb 1970 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Neutrino Emission ca 1960 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Neutrino/Antineutrino, B. Barish 1973 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Non-Relativistic Hydrogen Atom (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Notebook on Assorted Topics, QM, Computers etc. (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Notebook on Computers 1982-83 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Notebook on Particle Physics ca 1975 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Notebook on QCD and other topics ca 1987 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Notebook on Variational Principle [?] (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Notepad, Computer Applications and QCD (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Notepad on Computational Linguistics 1985 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Notepad on Gauge Transformations and QCD ca 1982 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Notepad on Miscellaneous Subjects (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Notepad on QED and Other Topics, Richard and Carl Feynman (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Notes, Concurrent QM Computation, Model of E. Coli August 1984 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Notes and Calculations, Mostly Gravitation [?] ca 1966 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Notes and Calculations, QCD, Computers [?] ca 198[?] (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Notes on Computers [?] ca 1983 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Notes on Various Subjects ca 1980s (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Nuclear Fluid (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Nuclear Physics (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Number Theory [?] (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Ongoing Proton (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Ordered Operators (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Origin of Mass and Other calculations (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Optics [?] ca 1980 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Pairs of Interacting Atoms/Oscillators [?] ca 1940s [?] (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Paper on Computer Character Recognition Program (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Particle Physics [?] (Box 73, Folder Folders 3-4)
    - Particle Physics, ερ?εΑΠζζ [?] ca 1969 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Particle Physics, Mesons, Coupling, Magnetic Moments (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Particle Physics Notes [?] ca 1977 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Particle Physics/Scattering Calculations ca 1967 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Particle Physics/Scattering Notes ca 1968 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Particle Tables 1973 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Particle Tables, Miscellaneous (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Parton and Hadron Collisions 1966-69 and undated (Box 74, Folder Folders 1-2)
    - Physics Reports 1973 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Plane waves, Dirac Case [?] (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - π⇒μ+υ 1958-1960 and undated (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Polarization, Huygens Principle (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Polarons (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Properties of Ψ, Ψ', ?( (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Properties of Matrix Elements Implied by [a(1), b(2)] 12/67 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Properties of the Function λ(χ)=-0ƒ;x[δυ/υ]×[λν(1-υ)] (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Properties of Stretched Surfaces [?] (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Protons October 1976 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - "Puzzles" File (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - QCD 3-Dimensions + Quarks [?] 1983 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - QCD and Partons Model 1978-79 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - QCD and Related Notes (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Quantum Mechanics [?] (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Quarks, Effects of Widths and Energies, etc. (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Quark Models ca 1970 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Radiation Formulae/ Nuclear Interactions ca 1945 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Radiation of Gravitational Waves 1961 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Regge via Harmonic Oscillators, M. Kislinger (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Resonant Scattering; Astrophysical Notes and Calculations ca 1972-73 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Scalar Electrodynamics, Strong Coupling [?] 6 Nov 1974 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Singer Index Theory (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Solid State and Quantum Mechanics, Mexico and South America [?] ca 1971-72 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Spin 1/2 Leading Terms (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Spin Annealing ca 1983 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Structure of Jet (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Summary of A. I. Material by Lenant ca 1984 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Summary of Formulas for Quantum Electrodynamics ca 1950 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Summary of Rosenfield Table, Baryons 5/26/69 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Symmetries of 3 Objects 5/24/69 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Theoretical Ideas Used in Analyzing Strange Particles (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - "The Qualitative Behavior of Yang-Mills Theory in 2+1 Dimensions" [published in Nuclear Physics B188, 1981] (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Transit of Venus (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Turbulence (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Two Component Equations (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Vacuum Polar: Pseudoscalar Mesons (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Vμυ(χ,χ′) (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Van der Waals Scattering (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Von Tilberg--Software Problems, Large Scale Software Systems ca 1983 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Vortex Line 10/26/67 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - WKB Theory (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Weak Decays (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Weisskopf Kuti Wave Functions 2/28/72 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - What is Intelligence and Related Notes on Artificial Intelligence (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - "Work on Computer" Notebook Oct 1973 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Yang-Mills (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Young Diagrams, Weak Interactions (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Section VIII: Work Of Others
    - Part A: Individuals, general
      - Alfaro, Fubini and Furlan 1979, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 1)
        - Preprints re Gravity
      - Anderson, Orson L. 1965, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2)
        - Notes, photocopies, reprints
      - Anderson, P. W. n.d. (Box 78, Folder 3)
        - Preprint
      - Barut, A. O. et al. 1984 (Box 78, Folder 4)
        - Reprint (photocopy) with Feynman's annotations re Dirac electron
      - Bjorken, J. D. and Eguchi, T. 1963, 1976, 1983 (Box 78, Folder 5)
        - Reprints (photocopies), correspondence (J. Zmuidzinas)
      - Blackmarr, Philip ca 1978-79 (Box 78, Folder 6)
        - Drawings
      - Bonic, Robert 1974 (Box 78, Folder 7)
        - Typescript (photocopy), correspondence
      - Botelho, Luiz C. L. n.d. (Box 78, Folder 8)
        - Preprint
      - Carlitz, R. and Kislinger, M. 1969 (Box 78, Folder 9)
        - Preprint
      - Coleman, Sidney 1975-1977 (Box 78, Folder 10)
        - Lecture transcripts (photocopies)
      - Dessler, A. J. 1961 (Box 78, Folder 11)
        - Reprint with Feynman's annotations and photo re cosmic radiation
      - Dimotakis, P. E. 1984 (Box 78, Folder 12)
        - Reprints
      - Dirac, P. A. M. 1931 (Box 78, Folder 13)
        - Article (photocopy)
      - DuMond, Jesse 1960 (Box 78, Folder 14)
        - Reprint
      - Einstein, Podolsky and Rosen 1935 (Box 78, Folder 15)
        - Article (photocopy)
      - Fadeev, L. et al. 1967, 1970-71 (Box 78, Folder 16)
        - Articles (photocopies)
      - Field, R. D. n.d. (Box 78, Folder 17)
        - [Notebook:] Quark/Proton/Model RPF & RDF
      - Field, R. D. 1974-75 (Box 78, Folder 18)
        - Notes by Field and Feynman, preprint and reprint (photocopies) re η-η′ mixing
      - Field, R. D. 1981 (Box 78, Folder 19)
        - Preprint
      - Field, R. D. Applications of Perturbative QCD (book MS) 1987 (Box 78, Folder Folders 20-21)
        - (folder 20) Typescript of Chaps. 1-3 with Feynman's annotations, correspondence; (folder 21) typescript of Chaps. 4-5 with Feynman's annotations
      - Field, R. D. Applications of Perturbative QCD (book MS) 1987 (Box 79, Folder 1)
        - Typescript of Chaps. 6-7, Appendix, with Feynman's annotations
      - Field, R. D. 1978 (Box 79, Folder 2)
        - Preprint
      - Fox, Geoffrey 1983, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 3)
        - Preprints with extensive annotations by Feynman, including letter to "Mr. Flynn"
      - Fradkin, E. S. et al. 1976-78 (Box 79, Folder 4)
        - Preprints, reprints
      - Frey, Alexander n.d. (Box 79, Folder 5)
        - Preprint re Hypercube
      - Fubini, S. et al. 1985 See also: Alfaro (Box 79, Folder 6)
        - Preprint, reprints (photocopies) re stochastics
      - Gell-Mann, Polyakov et al. 1975-76, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 7)
        - Typescript, reprint (photocopies) with Feynman's notes and annotations
      - Goodstein, D. 1975, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 8)
        - Articles (photocopies) re superfluid helium 3
      - Groenewold, H. J. 1946-1949 (Box 79, Folder 9)
        - Reprints
      - Hopfield, John 1982-83, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 10)
        - Preprints (photocopies), reprint
      - Jackiw, Roman et al. 1976-83 (Box 79, Folder 11)
        - Preprints, reprint, correspondence re Yang-Mills quantum theory, gauge theories
      - Julesz, Bela et al. 1974-81 (Box 79, Folder 12)
        - Reprints, correspondence re: biological cybernetics
      - Kikuchi, Ryoichi et al. 1951, 1967, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 1)
        - Reprints
      - Kosterlitz, J. and Thouless, D. J. 1972-73 (Box 80, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence, reprints
      - LaBerge, Stephen et al. 1980-81 (Box 80, Folder 3)
        - Preprints, reprints (some photocopy) re lucid dreaming
      - Langmuir, I. 1968 (Box 80, Folder 4)
        - Article (photocopy), annotated
      - LaRue, George et al. 1977-79 (Box 80, Folder 5)
        - Reprints (photocopies) with Feynman's annotations, dissertation, envelope
      - Mermin, N. D. 1981 (Box 80, Folder 6)
        - Article (photocopy); Feynman's notes, [1] leaf
      - Motin, Harry Chris n.d. (Box 80, Folder 7)
        - Typescript notes with Feynman's annotations; Feynman's notes, [1] leaf
      - Nemec, Donald 1976 (Box 80, Folder 8)
        - Typescript report re psychic phenomena
      - Platzman, P. et al. 1979 (Box 80, Folder 9)
        - Preprints, reprint
      - Poggio, T. et al. 1976-83 (Box 80, Folder 10)
        - Reprints (some photocopy); Feynman's notes, [1] leaf re biological cybernetics
      - Politzer, H. David 1974 (Box 80, Folder 11)
        - Reprint (photocopy) with Feynman's annotations (138v)
      - Politzer, H. David 1977 (Box 80, Folder 12)
        - Preprint
      - Polyakov, A. M. and Wiegman, P. B. ca 1983 (Box 80, Folder 13)
        - Preprint with Feynman's annotations re Goldstone bosons
        - Polyakov, A. M. See also: Gell-Mann
      - Privman, V. et al. ca 1985 (Box 80, Folder 14)
        - Preprint
        - Reines, F. See: Vogel, P.
      - Roshko, Anatol n.d. (Box 80, Folder 15)
        - Notes, [1] leaf; photos
      - Schwarz, John H. et al. 1980-81, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 16)
        - Preprints and reprint, with Feynman's annotations re superstrings
      - Scully, M. O. 1974 (Box 80, Folder 17)
        - Correspondence, preprints re superconductivity
      - Seitz, Charles 1984-85 (Box 80, Folder 18)
        - Correspondence, preprints, misc re Cosmic Cube
      - Sirri, N. n.d. (Box 80, Folder 19)
        - Technical Report "Inertial Sensors"
      - [Student notes, unidentified] 1983 (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Sutherland, Bill 1978 (Box 81, Folder 2)
        - Article (photocopy) re quantum soliton
      - t'Hooft, G. et al. 1971-72 (Box 81, Folder 3)
        - Articles (photocopies)
      - Thornber, K. K. n.d. (Box 81, Folder 4)
        - Preprint
      - Thorne, Kip 1981 (Box 81, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence, articles (photocopies)
      - Title, Allen 1966 (Box 81, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence, photos
      - Tuan, S. F. n.d. (Box 81, Folder 7)
        - Preprint
      - Van de Snepscheut, J. n.d. (Box 81, Folder 8)
        - Correspondence, notes
      - Vogel, P. et al. ca 1979-81 (Box 81, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence, typescripts, reprints; Feynman's notes, [2] leaves; misc re F. Reines, neutrino instability
      - Walker, R. L. 1969 (Box 81, Folder 10)
        - Reprint with Feynman's annotations
      - Wasserburg, G. J. et al. 1977 (Box 81, Folder 11)
        - Preprints
      - Weinberg, Steven 1975, n.d. (Box 81, Folder 12)
        - Preprints re bosons, symmetry breaking
      - Weisskopf, Victor 1974-81 (Box 81, Folder 13)
        - Preprint, reprint (photocopy)
      - Wilson, Kenneth G. 1972 (Box 81, Folder 14)
        - Transcript of lectures (photocopy) re QED
      - Wilson, Kenneth G. 1975 (Box 81, Folder 15)
        - Article (photocopy) re renormalization group
      - Wolfram, Stephen et al. ca 1978-79 (Box 81, Folder 16)
        - Preprints, reprints (photocopies), photos
      - Yariv, Amnon et al. 1977-79 (Box 82, Folder 1)
        - Reprints
      - Zewail, Ahmed at al. 1984 (Box 82, Folder 2)
        - Reprint, annotated
      - Zmuidzinas, J. See: Bjorken, J.D.
    - Part B: Subjects, general
      - [From envelope:] Acceleration temperature 1976-84 (Box 82, Folder 3)
        - Articles (photocopies)
      - Gauge theories, supersymmetry 1972-82, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 4)
        - Preprints, reprints; Feynman's notes on back of Lancet article
      - High energy physics, misc 1968-84 (Box 82, Folder 5)
        - Preprints, reprints, some with Feynman's annotations
      - Holography 1979-80 (Box 82, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence, reprints
      - Logic 1966-69 (Box 82, Folder 7)
        - Articles (photocopies)
      - Low temperature physics, misc 1982 (Box 82, Folder 8)
        - Article (photocopy)
      - Mayan (Dresden) codex 1986 (Box 82, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence, typescript
      - Miscellaneous 1951-85 (Box 82, Folder 10)
        - Preprints, reprints, articles (some photocopies)
      - Psychic phenomena 1982 (Box 82, Folder 11)
        - Article (photocopy) with Feynman's annotations
      - QCD, misc 1978-82 (Box 82, Folder 12)
        - Preprint, reprints
      - QED, misc 1961-83 (Box 82, Folder 13)
        - Preprints, reprints, articles (some photocopies)
      - Russian physicists, misc 1969-81, n.d. (Box 83, Folder 1)
        - Preprints, reprints (photocopies)
      - Solitons 1967-76 (Box 83, Folder 2)
        - Preprint, reprints (photocopies)
      - Superstrings 1984-85 (Box 83, Folder 3)
        - Preprints, reprints (photocopies) See also: Schwarz, John
      - [Unidentified book MS, incomplete] n.d. (Box 83, Folder 4)
        - Typescript with Feynman's annotations
      - [Unidentified book excerpt, in German, possibly Sophus Lie] (Box 83, Folder 5)
        - Photocopy with Feynman's annotations
    - Part C: Individuals, computer-related
      - Abelson, H. and Sussman, G. 1983 (Box 83, Folder 6)
        - Technical report, "Structure and Interpretation of Computer Programs," with notes by Feynman, [2] leaves
      - Bennett, Charles et al. 1973, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 7)
        - Preprints; notes by Feynman, [1] leaf
      - Chaitin, Gregory et al. 1965-75 (Box 83, Folder 8)
        - Preprints re information theory
      - Grossberg, Stephen 1982, n.d. (Box 84, Folder 1)
        - Preprints, reprints (photocopies) re cognitive theory
      - Hellwarth, R. W. et al. 1977-80 (Box 84, Folder 2)
        - Reprints re optics
      - Hewlett Packard calculator HP-28C 1987 (Box 84, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence, documents
      - Landauer, Rolf n.d. (Box 84, Folder 4)
        - Preprints re physical limits of computation
      - MIT Artificial Intelligence Laboratory, misc (Box 84, Folder Folders 5-6)
        - Reports, working papers
      - Mjolsness, Eric 1986 (Box 84, Folder 7)
        - Research report, documents re networks
    - Part D: Subjects, computer-related
      - Artificial intelligence, misc n.d. (Box 84, Folder 8)
        - Articles (photocopies)
      - Cellular automata 1984-85 (Box 84, Folder 9)
        - Articles (photocopies)
      - Computation, misc 1953-83, n.d. (Box 84, Folder 10)
        - Articles, preprints (photocopies) with Feynman's annotations
      - [Unidentified typescript] re connection machine ca 1985 [3] leaves (Box 84, Folder 11)
      - Conservative logic 1978-82 (Box 84, Folder 12)
        - Reprint, preprint with Feynman's annotations and notes, [2] leaves
      - Natural and artifical language 1968-77, n.d. (Box 84, Folder 13)
        - Reprints, preprints
      - Optical systems 1979-84 (Box 84, Folder 14)
        - Reprints
      - Programming ca 1981-82 (Box 85, Folder 1)
        - Articles (photocopies)
      - Simulated annealing 1982-84 (Box 85, Folder 2)
        - Research reports, IBM (photocopies)
      - Software development 1983 (Box 85, Folder 3)
        - Typescript by R. Van Tilburg with Feynman's annotations
      - Superconductivity 1979-84 (Box 85, Folder 4)
        - Reprints, articles (photocopies) with Feynman's annotations
      - Symbolic integration 1968-78 (Box 85, Folder 5)
        - Reprints (photocopies)
      - VLSI 1980 (Box 85, Folder 6)
        - Preprint, reprint with Feynman's annotations
    - Part E: Unsolicited MSS
      - Unsolicited MSS and correspondence 1973-87 (Box 85, Folder Folders 7-10)
        - (folder 7) A-D; (folder 8) E-G; (folder 9) H-L; (folder 10) M-Z
  - Section IX: Reprints And Books
    - Reprints, 1939-1955 (Box 86)
    - Reprints, 1956-1966 (Box 87)
    - Reprints, 1969-1974 (Box 88)
    - Reprints, 1976-1988 (Box 89)
    - Books (Box 90)
      - Alcantara Gomes Filho, Francisco. Física. Sao Paulo, 1947.
      - Cairns, J. et al., eds. Phage and the Origins of Molecular Biology. Cold Spring Harbor, 1966. [Presentation copy]
      - Chart of the Nuclides. General Electric, 1972. [Presentation copy]
      - Gaines, Helen. Elementary Cryptanalysis. Boston, 1943.
      - Kasten, Lloyd et al. Gato Preto. New York, 1947
      - Morris, Duncan Andrew. "The Relativistic String in the Caltech-II Model of Hadronization and Electron-Positron Annihilation." Ph.D. Dissertation, Caltech, 1987. (with RPF annotations)
      - Proceedings of the Conference on the Physics of Computation. International Journal of Theoretical Physics 21:3/4, 6/7, 12, 1982.
      - Review of Particle Properties. Physics Letters 75B:24 Apr 1978.
      - Wiezell, Elsa. Barro de Estrellas. Buenos Aires, 1951.
  - Section X: Oversize
    - Certificate, letter, and membership card from Pan American Airlines, 1949 (Box Oversize Box)
    - National Academy of Sciences, Diploma of Election to Fellow, 27 April 1954 (Box Oversize Box)
    - Venice Nobel Prize Scroll, 5 Feb 1958 (Box Oversize Box)
    - Printed matter: Revista de Revistas, 1972 (Box Oversize Box)
    - Feynman's slide rule (Box Oversize Box)
    - "We Love You, Dick" Photograph album donated by Juliana Christy (Oversize Item)
  - Section XI: Supplements
    - Supplement 1994
      - Proceedings of the Conference on the Role of Gravitation in Physics, Chapel Hill, March 1957 (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - Expanded version of remarks by RPF at Conference on the Role of Gravitation in Physics, Chapel Hill, March 1957 (typescript) (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Supplement 1996
      - Transcripts of talks
        - Feynman on "Viewpoint," KNXT-TV ca 1960 (Box 91, Folder 3)
        - Feynman at Far Rockaway H.S., 1960s (Box 91, Folder 4)
        - Nobel Prize dinner, Caltech 7 Jan 1966 (Box 91, Folder 5)
        - "Ground Zero" lecture 22 Apr 1982 (Box 91, Folder 6)
        - "The Pleasure of Finding Things Out" BBC 1981 (Box 91, Folder 6.1)
      - Physical Review
        - Volume 74, October 15, 1948 (Box 91, Folder 7)
        - Volume 74, November 15, 1948 (Box 91, Folder 8)
        - Volume 75, May 15, 1948 (Box 91, Folder 9)
        - Volume 21, July, 1949 (Box 91, Folder 10)
        - Volume 84, November 15, 1951 (Box 91, Folder 11)
        - Volume 85, January 15, 1952 (Box 91, Folder 12)
        - Volume 90, June 15, 1953 (Box 91, Folder 13)
        - Volume 91, September 15, 1953 (Box 92, Folder 1)
        - Volume 94, April 15, 1954 (Box 92, Folder 2)
        - Volume 102, June 1, 1956 (Box 92, Folder 3)
        - Volume 109, January 1, 1958 (Box 92, Folder 4)
        - Volume 129, March 15, 1963 (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous Publications
        - Kogut, John, and Leonard Susskind. The Parton Picture of Elementary Particles. Physics Reports 8C/2 (June, 1973). (Box 92, Folder 6)
        - Particle Data Group. Review of Particle Properties. Physics Letters 170B (April 10, 1986). (Box 92, Folder 7)